Bashour Tony Atrini

Full stack software engineer (JS, TS, React, Next.js, PHP, Laravel, AWS) experienced in developing B2B and B2C full-stack solutions with a passion for building applications that make a difference.

157 Al-Mushrif Abu Dhabi, Al Niwayi St +971 568 349 773 bashouratrini.dev@gmail.com LinkedIn/bashour-atrini GitHub/BashourDev

WORK EXPERIENCE

First Abu Dhabi Bank, Abu Dhabi — IT Consultant

Leading bank in the UAE June 2023 - present

- Improved the user experience by automating manual tasks and collaborating with multiple teams to accomplish various activities.
- Built scripts that performed tasks on over 5000 devices, which helped reduce the IT Service Desk and the End User Support load by ~20%.
- Provided application support and solutions for users bank-wide.

Swan Technology, Remote — Full-Stack *Software Engineer*

May 2020 - February 2023

- Built and maintained scalable and secure web and mobile applications across different sectors (e.g. Educational, Governmental, Retail, and Medical) using a variety of programming languages and frameworks (e.g. React, Express, PHP, Laravel, React Native, SQL, and more).
- Developed and trained machine learning models that scored ~97% accuracy and integrated them with existing web applications using Flask.

EDUCATION

Al-Hawash Private University, BSc in Informatics Engineering

EU Blue Card eligible university & degree. Top 10% of my class. 77% GPA. October 2017 - August 2022

PROJECTS

E-Commerce Website and Mobile App (2023). E-commerce store for a Dubai-based brand built with Shopify and React Native. The app and website provide a user-friendly and familiar shopping experience based on industry standards, which led to driving more business to the company.

COVID-19 Tracker (2021). Web application built for the Syrian Ministry of Health in association with a private hospital. The project aims to provide a central database for COVID-19 patients across all Syrian hospitals with an AI model to predict the treatment for each patient based on their medical history.

STACK

Proficient: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Next,js, React Native, Expo, PHP, Laravel, RESTful API, MySQL, Git, AWS

Familiar: Java, Python, C++

CERTIFICATES

Meta Front-End Developer Professional Certificate

AWARDS

Honored as an outstanding student in Al-Hawash Private University (2018) Ranked as one of the top 3 students in my class

LANGUAGES

Arabic native
English C1, advanced